Anna Liang

Intermediate Software Developer annaliang.contact@gmail.com
Toronto, ON

An experienced full-stack developer with a background in developing web and mobile applications in fast-paced, agile environments. Self-directed individual with a strong sense of ownership who takes initiative and efficiently manages work to achieve team objectives. Adept at collaborating with stakeholders to build out new features from its conception to deployment while consistently prioritizing the end-user experience.



Skills:

- React/React Native
- Redux
- TypeScript
- JavaScript
- Node.js
- Express
- HTML/CSS
- MongoDB
- REST API
- Python
- Git
- GCP
- SQL
- Java
- Mocha
- Docker



Education:

University of Toronto

Bachelor of Science: Computer Science

September 2017 - April 2021 | Toronto, ON



Work Experience:

Moves / Toronto (May 2022 - December 2023)

Junior Software Developer (May 2022 - May 2023) Intermediate Software Developer (May 2023 - Dec 2023)

- Spearheaded two major front-end mobile application rebrandings to update the overall look and theme to new specifications
- Proposed and delivered a solution to aggregate thousands of data points into weekly and annual views to unlock insights for end users
- Demonstrated a commitment to continual growth by leading and knowledge sharing during front-end skill-up sessions with the engineering team

Index Exchange / Toronto (January 2020 - April 2020)

Software Engineer

- Implemented new internal application for accumulating and forwarding Jira data to Domo - enabling flexible metric calculations and visualizations
- Orchestrated efficient software design, development, and deployment with Docker, including testing features and reviewing code



Technical Projects:

La Room de Discode

- Built a collaborative videotelephony editor using Express,
 React, Node.js, MongoDB, and GraphQL
- Integrated real time synchronization with a shared Python IDE and shell, as well as video, audio, and chat communication using WebRTC and WebSockets